<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Central Michigan's Best Real Estate Training</title>
    <description>Mary Peacock, a top Real Estate Agent in Central Michigan, shares her own internal real estate agent training for free. Her Real Estate Training, Tips and Advice will help you sell more homes in less time.</description>
    <link>https://midmichiganrealestatecareers.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="https://midmichiganrealestatecareers.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jan 2019 10:51:23 -0600</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Jan 2019 10:51:23 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.2.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Few Tips for Staying in Touch With Your Database</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/ot0yWYr7wHU?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today I want to talk to you about staying in touch with your database.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I haven’t done a great job at keeping up with my database in the past. I’ll be the first to admit that. &lt;strong&gt;However, here’s what I’ve done to improve that since.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I make sure that I send my database something of value to them on a regular basis.&lt;/strong&gt; I send out videos twice a month that give real estate tips for buyers, sellers, and everyone in between. I also hold client events three times per year and make sure to invite everyone in the database. A lot of our clients really enjoy these events.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=My database always appreciates knowing what the market is doing.%20https://midmichiganrealestatecareers.com/a-few-tips-for-staying-in-touch-with-your-database.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“My database always appreciates knowing what the market is doing.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Finally, I send out market reports once a month to my database.&lt;/strong&gt; They always appreciate knowing what the market is doing and what the current equity in their home looks like.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions for me or want any more tips, don’t hesitate to give me a call or send me an email. I look forward to hearing from you soon.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 18 Dec 2018 13:46:26 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>https://midmichiganrealestatecareers.com/a-few-tips-for-staying-in-touch-with-your-database.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://midmichiganrealestatecareers.com/a-few-tips-for-staying-in-touch-with-your-database.html</guid>
        
        <category>Database</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
