<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:itunesu="http://www.itunesu.com/feed" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Central Michigan Real Estate Mentoring Podcast with Mary Peacock</title>
    <link>https://midmichiganrealestatecareers.com</link>
    <atom10:link xmlns:atom10="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://midmichiganrealestatecareers.com"/>
    <description>Looking for more ways to grow your real estate business and increase your income? Mary Peacock, founder of Peacock Real Estate, shares her success stories and strategies to help you on your path to a successful real estate career. For even more information and tips, go to MidMichiganRealEstateCareers.com, and follow her mentoring Facebook page https://www.facebook.com/midmichiganrealestatecareers. Ready to take your career to the next level? Peacock Real Estate provides exceptional training and mentoring to help your real estate business thrive! Call 231-856-4456 for more information!</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <managingEditor>Mary Peacock</managingEditor>
    <lastBuildDate>2019-01-24 13:20:09 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <media:copyright>Mary Peacock</media:copyright>
    <media:thumbnail url="https://midmichiganrealestatecareers.com/img/podcast.jpg"/>
    <media:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Central Michigan, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</media:keywords>
    <media:category scheme="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd">Education</media:category>
    <itunes:owner>
      <itunes:email>Mary@PeacockRealEstate.com</itunes:email>
      <itunes:name>Mary Peacock</itunes:name>
    </itunes:owner>
    <itunes:author>Mary Peacock</itunes:author>
    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    <itunes:image href="https://midmichiganrealestatecareers.com/img/podcast.jpg"/>
    <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Central Michigan, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
    <itunes:subtitle>Learn all the tips, tricks and more for buyers and sellers in the Central Michigan Area Real Estate Market</itunes:subtitle>
    <itunes:summary>Looking for more ways to grow your real estate business and increase your income? Mary Peacock, founder of Peacock Real Estate, shares her success stories and strategies to help you on your path to a successful real estate career. For even more information and tips, go to MidMichiganRealEstateCareers.com, and follow her mentoring Facebook page https://www.facebook.com/midmichiganrealestatecareers. Ready to take your career to the next level? Peacock Real Estate provides exceptional training and mentoring to help your real estate business thrive! Call 231-856-4456 for more information!</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:category text="Education"/>
    
      <item>
        <title>Is Now a Good Time to Get Into Real Estate?</title>
        <link>https://midmichiganrealestatecareers.com/is-now-a-good-time-to-get-into-real-estate.html</link>
        
        <author>Mary Peacock</author>
        <pubDate>2019-01-17 13:48:53 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Mary+Peacock/West+Central+Michigan+Real+Estate+Agent-+Is+Now+a+Good+Time+to+Get+Into+Real+Estate_.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Many people are wondering whether now is a good time to get started in real estate. Here’s the truth: If you’ve been considering a career in this industry, there’s no time like the present. Real estate is a challenging industry, but it’s also a rewarding one. There are endless opportunities for those willing to work for the potential rewards of a real estate career. I would be more than happy to speak with you about these opportunities, so feel free to get in touch.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Mary+Peacock/West+Central+Michigan+Real+Estate+Agent-+Is+Now+a+Good+Time+to+Get+Into+Real+Estate_.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="https://midmichiganrealestatecareers.com" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Mary+Peacock/West+Central+Michigan+Real+Estate+Agent-+Is+Now+a+Good+Time+to+Get+Into+Real+Estate_.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>If you’ve ever wondered whether it’s a good time to get into real estate, then today’s message is for you.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Mary Peacock</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>If you’ve ever wondered whether it’s a good time to get into real estate, then today’s message is for you.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Central Michigan, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>How Mary Peacock Got into Real Estate</title>
        <link>https://midmichiganrealestatecareers.com/how-mary-peacock-got-into-real-estate.html</link>
        
        <author>Mary Peacock</author>
        <pubDate>2019-01-15 14:17:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="https://midmichiganrealestatecareers.com" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>
</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Mary Peacock</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>
</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Central Michigan, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Essential Apps for Real Estate Agents!</title>
        <link>https://midmichiganrealestatecareers.com/essential-apps-for-real-estate-agents.html</link>
        
        <author>Mary Peacock</author>
        <pubDate>2019-01-11 13:59:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>Leveraging technology helps you build a profitable real estate business! But with so many apps to choose from, where do you start? You might already have more apps on your phone than you ever use. So before we dive into my list of essential apps, here are three tips that will help you use them as effectively as possible:


  
    Remove the apps you never use. Clean house on your smartphone! Visual clutter makes it harder to find the go-to apps that you need the most. 
  
  
    Set a monthly technology budget within your business expense budget. In some cases, an app itself is free, or has a free trial, but then a monthly cost applies. It’s easy to rack up several monthly app fees before you know it, so choose wisely! 
  
  
    Choose apps that best solve ongoing issues that you’re likely to face in your business. Keep your bottom line in mind. Ask yourself: “Will this app allow me to give better service to my clients? Will this app save me money? Will it help me make money? Will it help me stay top-of-mind with my clients?”Here is the list of apps that I’ve put together. This isn’t all-inclusive, but they’re good, practical apps that most real estate agents will find beneficial. 
  


Dropbox: This cloud-based service stores, synchronizes, and shares files from your smartphone, PC, and tablet. It allows users to scan and store contact lists, contracts, appraisals, and more —  including PDFs, Word documents, and spreadsheets, as well as listing photos, Adobe files, videos, and other relevant files. This app is a great way to save important client and property information on the go. A basic account with 2 GB of storage is free.

Docusign: A must-have for agents in the digital age, this app allows you to upload and send documents for signature. You can also send reminders and verify signing status anytime. NAR members can get a discounted subscription.

Expensify: Scan business expense receipts using your smartphone using this app, which codes and categorizes expenditures for you. This makes for easy itemization come tax time. Plus, it can track business miles using GPS technology. The app is free to download, but a small monthly fee does apply. 

Inkly: Mail greeting cards and thank-you cards to clients using this app. It uses your own handwriting! Write your message on a piece of paper, snap a photo of it with your smartphone, and upload to Inkly. Inkly prints it on quality cardstock and mails it for you. 

Magicplan: Create floor plans and virtual tours using your smartphone. You can also create 3-D floorplans! Monthly fees vary according to the type of account you choose. 

One last tip: Pick one app today, and practice using it. Once you’re comfortable with it, incorporate it into your business routine! After you’ve mastered your first app, you can begin using others (one at a time) and establish proficiency with each of them over time.

But remember when using these apps to keep their monthly fees, as well as their terms of use and cancellation policies, in mind.

Looking for more ways to grow your real estate business and increase your income? See my strategies at MidMichiganRealEstateCareers.com, and follow the Facebook page, https://www.facebook.com/midmichiganrealestatecareers/!Ready to take your career to the next level? Peacock Real Estate provides exceptional training and mentoring to help your real estate business thrive! Call 231-856-4456 or message me for more information!
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="https://midmichiganrealestatecareers.com" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Leveraging technology helps you build a profitable real estate business! But with so many apps to choose from, where do you start? You might already have more apps on your phone than you ever use. So before we dive into my list of essential apps, here are three tips that will help you use them as effectively as possible:

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Mary Peacock</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Leveraging technology helps you build a profitable real estate business! But with so many apps to choose from, where do you start? You might already have more apps on your phone than you ever use. So before we dive into my list of essential apps, here are three tips that will help you use them as effectively as possible:

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Central Michigan, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>A Few Tips for Staying in Touch With Your Database</title>
        <link>https://midmichiganrealestatecareers.com/a-few-tips-for-staying-in-touch-with-your-database.html</link>
        
          <category>Database</category>
        
        <author>Mary Peacock</author>
        <pubDate>2018-12-18 13:46:26 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Celeste+Zarling/West+Central+Michigan+Real+Estate+Agent-+A+Few+Tips+for+Staying+in+Touch+With+Your+Database.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Today I want to talk to you about staying in touch with your database.

I haven’t done a great job at keeping up with my database in the past. I’ll be the first to admit that. However, here’s what I’ve done to improve that since.

I make sure that I send my database something of value to them on a regular basis. I send out videos twice a month that give real estate tips for buyers, sellers, and everyone in between. I also hold client events three times per year and make sure to invite everyone in the database. A lot of our clients really enjoy these events.

“My database always appreciates knowing what the market is doing.”

Finally, I send out market reports once a month to my database. They always appreciate knowing what the market is doing and what the current equity in their home looks like.

If you have any questions for me or want any more tips, don’t hesitate to give me a call or send me an email. I look forward to hearing from you soon. 
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Celeste+Zarling/West+Central+Michigan+Real+Estate+Agent-+A+Few+Tips+for+Staying+in+Touch+With+Your+Database.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="https://midmichiganrealestatecareers.com" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Celeste+Zarling/West+Central+Michigan+Real+Estate+Agent-+A+Few+Tips+for+Staying+in+Touch+With+Your+Database.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Our database is a huge source of business for us. Here’s how we stay in touch with them.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Mary Peacock</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Our database is a huge source of business for us. Here’s how we stay in touch with them.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Central Michigan, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
    <copyright>Mary Peacock</copyright>
    <media:credit role="author">Mary Peacock</media:credit>
    <media:rating>nonadult</media:rating>
    <media:description type="plain">Looking for more ways to grow your real estate business and increase your income? Mary Peacock, founder of Peacock Real Estate, shares her success stories and strategies to help you on your path to a successful real estate career. For even more information and tips, go to MidMichiganRealEstateCareers.com, and follow her mentoring Facebook page https://www.facebook.com/midmichiganrealestatecareers. Ready to take your career to the next level? Peacock Real Estate provides exceptional training and mentoring to help your real estate business thrive! Call 231-856-4456 for more information!</media:description>
  </channel>
</rss>
